-莫妮卡呢  -她在家
- Where's Mon? - She's at home..
布置瑞秋今晚的生日派对
putting up decorations for Rachel's birthday party tonight.
-你不用帮忙吗  -我有试过
- You're not helping? - I tried..
但是  显然
but apparently
用假音唱《我会活下去》可帮不上忙
singing "I Will Survive" in a helium voice,not helping.
-嘿  你们好  -嘿
- Hey,guys. - Hey.
祝你生日...
Happy birthday to...
别说那么大声  甘瑟会过来抱我的
Don't say that loud. Gunther's gonna want to hug me.
好消息  我们终于找到保姆了
Good news,everyone. We finally found a nanny.
这位是莫莉
This is Molly.
莫莉  来见过钱德勒  乔伊
Molly,Chandler,Joey.
有人有点不高兴哦
Somebody's getting a little fussy.
你说的没错  我就是不高兴
You're damn right I am.
我已经等饼干等了七分钟了
I've been waiting for a cookie for seven minutes.
好了  我想我带她出去好了
Okay. You know what,I'm just gonna take her outside.
不  你留下来  我去
No,you stay. I'll do it.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
-很高兴认识你们  -是啊  我们也是
- Nice to meet you guys. - Yeah,you too.
-哇  莫莉真的很不错  -是啊
- Wow,Molly's just great. - Yeah.
是啊  真棒  请了个性感保姆
Yes,bravo on the hot nanny.
什么 你真觉得她很性感吗
What? You really think she's hot?
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
如果我未婚  她现在就在拒绝我了
If I wasn't married,she'd be rejecting me right now.
乔伊
Joey?
觉得她的姿势怎样
How do you think she's doing?
我是唯一不觉得她性感的吗  罗斯
Am I the only one that doesn't think she's hot? Ross?
我觉得  她不是没有魅力  但是
I mean,she's not unattractive,but..
但是性感嘛
but hot?
谢谢你
Thank you.
瑞秋走了  说吧
Now that Rachel's gone?
她真性感  我昨晚是哭着入睡的
So hot,I cried myself to sleep last night.
嘿  麦克  秘鲁的首都是哪里
Hey,Mike,what's the capital of Peru?
-利马  -不是
- Lima. - No.
是V开头X结尾的字
It starts with a V and ends with an X.
然后最好中间有T和O
And hopefully with a T-O in the middle.
我仔细想想之后
You know,come to think of it,
秘鲁的首都应该叫"VTOX"
the capital of Peru is "Vtox."
-哦  天啊 -怎么了
- Oh,God! - What?
好了  我不想要吓坏你
Okay. I don't want to freak you out or anything..
但是我刚在柜子里看到一只老鼠
but I just saw a rat in your cupboard.
哦  是哦  那是鲍伯
Oh,yeah. No,that's Bob.
是你的宠物鼠吗
Well,he's your pet rat?
不太算是  只是偶尔会来拜访
Well,not so much a pet as,you know,an occasional visitor..
我有时候会喂他  有点像圣诞老人
who I put food out for. Kind of like Santa.
不过圣诞老人不会在饼干盘里便便
Except Santa doesn't poop on the plate of cookies.
你不能在公寓里养老鼠
You can't keep a rat in your apartment.
那很不卫生的
They're extremely unsanitary.
它们会传染细螺旋体病或是汉滩病毒
I mean,they transmit leptospirosis and hantavirus.
-那是什么  -我不知道
What are those? - I don't know..
但听起来可不像是温泉疗养
but they don't sound like spa treatments.
-你必须处理掉他  -好啦
- You have to get rid of it. - Okay,fine.
如果你这么在乎  我会处理掉鲍伯的
If it means that much to you,I'll get rid of Bob.
谢谢你
Thank you.
真奇怪  你觉得他很恶心
It's so weird you think he's so gross,
却又在吃他的饼干
yet you're willing to eat his crackers.
加文  我想再次跟你道谢
Gavin,I just want to say thank you again..
谢谢昨天帮我照顾艾玛
for watching Emma yesterday during the presentation.
我真的需要跟你道歉
I really owe you an apology.
道什么歉
For what?
当我们第一次见面时  你知道的
When we first met,you know..
我以为你是自负  高傲又讨人厌的人
I thought you were pompous and arrogant and obnoxious.
你待会儿又得接着道歉吧
Is this your first apology?
不  我只是想说
No,I just mean,you know,
第一印象通常不是很重要的
first impressions don't mean anything.
而我认为你是个好男人
And I think you're a really good guy.
很抱歉我错看了你
And I'm sorry that I misjudged you.
-早安  -嗨
- Morning. - Hello.
我想说  新的一天  新的开始
But you know what? Hey,new day,new leaf.
我只是真的很高兴
I am just really,really happy..
我很抱歉  显然
I'm sorry. Obviously,
海瑟的屁股有更重要的事要对你说
Heather's ass has something more important to say..
我先让它说完好了
so I'll just wait till it's finished.
-什么  -我正在跟你道歉
- What? - I was giving you an apology..
而你一直在打量她
and you were totally checking her out.
我没有  我在时装业工作
I wasn't. I'm in fashion.
我只是在看她的裙子
I was looking at her skirt.
貌似是裤子吧  我并没有看清楚
Or was it pants? I didn't really see
屁股以下的部位
what happened below the ass area.
哇  你真的是  你真恶心
Wow,you are really.. You're really a creep.
就算我是在看她  你又在乎什么呢
What do you care if I was looking at her?
你是在忌妒吗
Are you jealous?
哦  是啊  我好忌妒
Oh,yeah. I'm jealous.
"哦  加文  拜托请看看我的屁股"
"Oh,Gavin. Please,please look at my ass."
不要看我的屁股
Stop looking at my ass!
我只是认为这样的行为是不妥的
I mean,I just think you are totally inappropriate. Okay?
这是工作场所  她是你下属
This is a work environment. She's your subordinate.
但你跟你前助理泰格上床就可以吗
But it was okay when you slept with your old assistant,Tag?
那完全不一样  原因有二
That is totally different for two reasons.
一  我不知道你知道那件事
One: I didn't know that you knew that.
二  我不是盯着他屁股看的恶心人
And two: I wasn't some creep staring at his ass.
我们有很深入  有意义的交往
We had a.. We had a deep,meaningful relationship.
泰格姓什么
What was Tag's last name?
是...
It was..
哦  我的天
Oh,my God.
他没有  他没有 他没有姓
He didn't.. He didn't.. He didn't have a last name.
就叫泰格而已  就像雪儿  或是
It was just Tag,you know,like Cher or..
摩西
you know,Moses.
但那是很深入  有意义的交往
But it was a deep,meaningful relationship.
好吧  我对你的第一印象完全正确
You know what? My first impression of you was absolutely right.
你高傲  又自负
You are arrogant. You are pompous.
摩根  摩根
Morgan! Morgan!
-泰格姓摩根 -是琼斯
- Tag's last name was Morgan! - It was Jones.
你是谁啊  他男朋友吗
What are you,his boyfriend?
天啊  我希望我有个像你一样的保姆
Man,I wish I had a nanny like you.
你是说你小时候吗
You mean when you were a baby?
当然
Sure.
你可不可以别再盯着她看
Would you stop staring at her?
我没有盯着
I wasn't staring.
我是斜眼瞄着
I was leering.
她有什么了不起的呢
What's the big deal with her?
或许她有很抢眼的魅力
Maybe she's attractive in an obvious kind of way.
是啊  抢眼的魅力最糟糕了
Yeah,obvious beauty's the worst.
你知道的  当它就显现在你面前时
You know,when it's right there in your face.
我比较喜欢渐渐去发掘一个人的魅力
Me,I like to have to work to find someone attractive.
让我感觉像是我辛苦得来的
Makes me feel like I earned it.
看起来乔伊好像跟她处的不错
Looks like Joey's doing all right with her.
是啊  你们两个这次愿意退让出
Yeah. Hey,that was nice of you guys to back off..
让乔伊去泡她  真是好心
and let Joey get the girl for once.
我要带她回去了
I'm gonna take her to the apartment.
好的  我下班之后就回去
Okay. I'll be home right after work.
-好的 -好的  艾玛  再见
- Okay. - Okay,bye,Emma.
我爱你
I love you.
-再见 -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
他们推选我来跟你说
They've elected me to talk to you
你模仿婴儿说话的事
about the baby talk.
大家不是很喜欢
It's not so good.
我觉得挺可爱的
I think it's sweet.
再见  艾玛
Bye,Emma!
嘿  乔伊  关于莫莉
Hey,listen,Joey. About Molly,
我希望你不要去动她
I would really prefer if you didn't go after her.
为什么不行
Why not?
因为我们花了好几个月才找到好保姆
It took months to find a good nanny.
而我不希望有任何事情让她离开
And I wouldn't want anything to,you know,drive her away.
所以你认为我只会跟她上床
So you think I'm just gonna sleep with her..
之后就不再打电话给她
and never call her again,
让一切都变得很尴尬吗
and things are gonna get uncomfortable?
是啊  听起来好像也对
Yeah,that sounds about right.
别这样  外面到处都是女人
Come on,there are plenty of other women out there.
别打她的主意  不可以碰她
Just forget about her,okay? She's off-limits.
天啊  你为什么要这样说呢
Oh,man! What'd you have to go and say that for?
你越说我不可以碰她
Now that you told me I can't have her,
我就越想要她了
makes me want her even more!
-你还是小孩啊  -是的
- What are you,a child? - Yes!
听着  乔伊  别这样  为了我  拜托
Look,Joey,come on now. For me,please.
把你的性能量转移到别人身上
Just try to focus your sexual energy on someone else.
好啦
Fine.
带我回家吧
Take me home.
-嘿  麦克  -嘿  菲比
- Hey,Mikey. - Hey,Phoebe.
-你在做什么呢  -放捕鼠器
- What are you doing? - Setting rattraps.
要杀鲍伯吗
To kill Bob?
不是  只是测试一下他脖子有多硬
No. No,to test his neck strength.
不  我不想杀死他
No,I don't want to kill him.
我以为我们要活抓他
I thought we were gonna capture him..
然后到乡下把他放生
and,you know,set him free in the countryside..
让他可以认识友善的负鼠
where he could meet a friendly possum..
或是爱说笑的猫头鹰
and a wisecracking owl.
好了  我把捕鼠器丢掉
Okay,okay. I'll throw away the traps.
好  我会找到鲍伯  我会抓到他的
All right,I'll find Bob. I'll get him.
鲍伯  鲍伯
Bob? Bob?
罗伯特
Robert?
等等  我听到他的声音了
Wait,I think I hear him.
天啊  鲍伯生小孩了 鲍伯当妈妈了
Oh,my God! Bob had babies! Bob's a mom!
我们得替她改名字了
We'll have to think of a new name.
我不知道  我喜欢"鲍伯"当女生名字
I don't know,I kind of like "Bob" for a girl.
不不  我是说我不确定我们
No,no. I mean,I'm not sure that we..
天啊  我们杀了鲍伯吗
Oh,my God. We killed Bob?
或许不是鲍伯  或许只是只老鼠
Well,maybe it wasn't Bob. Maybe it was a mouse.
苏西
Susie?
怎么样
What's up?
说真的  老兄  三年了
Seriously,dude. Three years ago.
听着  你可以帮我一个忙吗
Listen,can you do me a favor?
我今天要出去
I'm gonna be out today.
你可以帮我看着乔伊
Can you keep an eye on Joey..
确保他跟莫莉之间不会出事吗
make sure nothing happens between him and Molly?
-你不相信他吗  -不相信
- You don't trust him? - Well,no.
有个听起来很像乔伊声音的女人
Some woman who sounded a lot like Joey
之前打电话来
called earlier..
要找她称之为"性感保姆"的女儿
and asked for her daughter,the "hot nanny."
你打算让我长期干预他们吗
Is this your long-term plan,for me to run interference?
我可能随时都会找到工作的
Because I could get a job any day now.
你在某些方面真是拔尖人才
You do appear right on the cusp of something.
听着  拜托  老兄
Look,come on,man.
我确定他一两星期后就会没兴趣了
I'm sure he'll lose interest in a week or two..
但是目前  你可以帮我这个忙吗
but for now,could you please just do this for me?
好啦  但是如果失败可别怪我哦
Fine,but don't blame me if it doesn't work.
因为你也了解  乔伊一旦下定决心
Because you know once Joey sets his mind on something..
无论如何  他都会把她搞上手的
more often than not,he's going to have sex with it.
那我们得要做点什么  不是吗
Well,I mean,we've gotta do something. Okay?
她那样的保姆可不是树上凭空长出来的
Nannies like her don't grow on trees.
-在想像那棵树吗  -是的  没错
- Picturing that tree? - I am,yes.
你要去哪  乔
Where you going,Joe?
去散步
For a walk.
我也去好吗
You mind if I join you?
事实上  我想要一个人去
Actually,I'd rather be alone.
我真的需要理清一些想法
You know,I really need to organize my thoughts.
一"些"想法
Your thoughts?
复数的
Plural?
好啦  我只有一个想法
All right,fine. I only have one thought.
就是关于那个性感保姆  我必须见到她
It's about the hot nanny! I gotta see her!
恐怕我不能让你去  乔伊
I'm afraid I can't let you do that,Joe.
你是说我不能见她
Now you're saying I can't see her?
你简直让我生不如死
You're killing me!
她就像是禁果  就像是...
She's forbidden fruit! It's like,like..
她是公主  而我是马童
like she's the princess and I'm the stable boy.
为什么你要这样
Why are you doing this,huh?
是不是罗斯要你别让我过去的呢
Did Ross tell you not to let me go over there?
没错  事实上的确如此
Yes,as a matter of fact,he did.
所以我不能让你过去
So I can't let you go.
有趣  现在出现挡路的了
Interesting. Now there are obstacles.
性感保姆和我一起抵抗全世界
Hot nanny and me against the world!
伟大的爱情小说就源自类似的生活故事
This is the stuff great novels are made of.
伟大的爱情小说?
Great novels?
好啦  二流的情色书刊
Fine. Mediocre porn.
加文·米奇办公室
Gavin Mitchell's office.
瑞秋·格林办公室
Rachel Greene's office.
电话给我
Give me that phone.
嗨  我是瑞秋·格林  可以为您效劳吗
Hello,this is Rachel Greene. How can I help you?
好的  我会把电话传给你儿子
Okay then. I'll pass you back to your son.
妈  不是  她只是我的秘书
Hey,Mom. No,that's just my secretary.
不好意思  加文
Excuse me,Gavin.
我有个问题必须要问你
I have a question I need to ask you.
妈  我再回电给你  是的
Mom,I'll call you later. Yeah.
-怎样  -如果你那么喜欢看屁股
- Yes? - If you like looking at butts so much..
你何不自己去照镜子呢
why don't you just go look in a mirror?
感谢上帝  你终于说了
Thank God you finally said that.
三小时前我就看到你写在笔记本上了
I saw you make a note on your pad three hours ago.
天啊  我真的惹你厌  是不是
Man,I really bug you. Don't I?
哦  不  拜托
Oh,no. Please..
我根本不在乎你  更别提讨厌你
I don't care about you enough to bug me.
事实上  从现在开始
In fact,from now on,
我会表现的很有格调
I'm going to take the high road..
而且我会对你非常好  妈妈的乖宝宝
and I'm going to be very,very nice to you,you mama's boy..
从现在开始
starting right now.
-嘿  瑞秋  -嗨
- Hey,Rach. - Hi.
准备好要吃生日午餐了吗
Ready for your birthday lunch?
好了  好了
I am. I am.
但是首先  莫妮卡 我想要介绍你认识
But first,Monica,I would like to introduce you..
我非常能干的同事  而且更重要的是
to my very talented colleague and more importantly..
我的好朋友  加文·米奇
my wonderful friend,Gavin Mitchell.
-幸会  -幸会
- Pleased to meet you. - Pleased to meet you.
你会来参加瑞秋的派对吗
Are you coming to Rachel's party?
哦  不不不不
Oh,no,no,no,no.
加文去不成  他已经有计划了
Gavin can't. He already has plans..
应该是要去看他妈妈
most likely with his mother.
我不介意  我可以取消
I don't mind. I'll cancel them.
我不想错过我秘书的生日
I would never miss my secretary's birthday.
为什么你要邀请他
Why did you invite him?
我无法忍受那个男的
I can't stand that guy!
你看起来跟他很好啊
You were being so nice to him.
我是装出来的
I was faking it.
你难道看不出来我是装的吗
Can't you tell when I'm being fake?
嘿  菲利浦先生  西装真帅
Hey,Mr. Phillips. Nice suit.
抓到了  装出来的恭维话
Right there. That was so fake!
我真不敢相信  你邀请了加文
I still can't believe you invited Gavin.
他是我最不想见到的人
He is just the last person I want to see.
"不用谢我帮你办派对"
You're welcome for the party.
我很高兴你玩得开心
I'm glad you're having a good time.
我希望他不要出现
I hope he doesn't show up.
他当然不会  他讨厌我
Of course he won't,the guy hates me.
-是吗  -什么
- Does he? - What?
或许他一直惹你生气  是因为喜欢你
Maybe he keeps bothering you so much because he likes you.
就像在小学一年级的时候
It's like in first grade
斯库普·郎把我推倒在操场上
when Skippy Lange would always push me on the playground
其实是因为他在暗恋我
because he secretly had a crush on me.
莫妮卡  你以为斯库普喜欢你吗
Monica,you think Skippy liked you?
亲爱的  所有的男生都在打赌
Honey,all those boys had a bet
看他是不是有办法撂倒你
to see if he could knock you over.
她睡了  我带她回去
She's out. I'm gonna take her home.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
再见  甜心
Bye,sweetheart.
男人都觉得她很有魅力  你有发现吗
Do you see what all the guys see in her?
至少不会想踢她下床
Wouldn't kick her out of bed.
我不可以再喝伏特加了
No more vodka for me.
嘿  瑞秋
Hey,Rach.
现在可以唱生日快乐歌了吗
So can I sing "Happy Birthday" to you now?
-当然可以 -好的
- Yeah,sure. - All right.
祝你生日...
Happy birthday to....
待会见
See you later.
瑞秋  有人送你鞋子
Hey,Rach. Somebody got you shoes.
快给我看
Give me!
-哇哇  我的天啊  -小心小心
- Wow. Wow. Oh,my God! - Careful! Careful!
里面是我的老鼠宝宝
These are my rat babies!
是啊  我们现在有老鼠宝宝了
Yeah. We have rat babies now.
你带老鼠来参加我的生日派对
You brought rats to my birthday party?
原来中风是这种感觉啊
So this is what a stroke feels like.
我必须要带着他们  我们杀了他们的妈
Well,I had to bring them. We killed their mother.
他们现在是我们的责任了
They're our responsibility now.
你知道的  他们需要一直被照顾
You know,they require constant care.
你应该知道的  瑞秋  你自己也是母亲
You should know that, Rachel, you're a mother.
你把我女儿跟一只老鼠做比较
Are you comparing my daughter to a rat?
不  是七只
No. Seven rats.
我们应该带他们回家了
We should take them home.
他们需要吃东西了
We need to feed them.
你竟然要离开我的派对
You're gonna leave my party
回去照顾一盒老鼠
to take care of a box of rats?
嗯  我很抱歉  瑞秋
Well,I'm sorry,Rachel,
但是我不像你  好吗
but I'm not like you. Okay?
不是每个人都请得起保姆的
Not everyone can afford help.
嘿  乔伊跟莫莉去哪了
Hey,where the hell are Joey and Molly?
我要你看住他们的
I asked you to watch them.
我很抱歉  我有点分心了
I'm sorry. I got a little preoccupied.
听着  我们及时阻止他们  以免出事
Look,we have to stop them before something happens.
我会追随你的  大哥
Right behind you,big guy.
所以你瞧  莫莉  人们不了解
So you see,Molly,what people don't understand..
演戏也是一门学科
is that acting is a discipline.
需要很辛苦的学习和付出
It takes a lot of hard work.
所以你是在哪里学的
So where'd you study?
我没有上过大学
I didn't go to college.
那  是从哪里学会演戏的呢
No,where'd you study acting?
莫莉  演戏不是学来的
Molly,people don't study acting.
莫莉  可以让我们谈几分钟吗
Molly,do you mind giving us just a minute?
-当然  我去看艾玛  -谢谢
- Sure. I'll go check on Emma. - Thanks.
马童就不能得到公主吗
Will the stable boy never get the princess?
你以为你接下来会发生什么
What do you think you were gonna do,
在我家沙发上跟她作爱
have sex with her right here on my couch?
不  沙发皮会黏住我的屁股
No. The leather sticks to my ass.
真不公平
You know, This isn't fair.
你凭什么认为我会跟她上床
What makes you think I'm gonna sleep with her..
然后就抛弃她呢
and then blow her off,huh?
你们难道不能敞开心胸接受
Can't you guys open your minds to the possibility
或许我是真的喜欢她
that I actually like her..
而且想来段真感情
and might want something real?
听着  事实上
Look,the truth is,
自从瑞秋之后
I haven't felt this way
我就没有对任何人有过这种感觉了
about anyone since Rachel.
好吗  我以为我不会再爱了
Okay? I didn't think I could ever love again.
-少来了 -乔伊
- Come on! - Joe!
嗨  莫莉在吗
Hi. Is Molly here?
在  请进  莫莉
Yeah,yeah. Come on in. Molly?
-嘿  各位  这位是塔比莎  -嘿
- Hey. Guys,this is Tabitha. - Hey.
-明天见  -好的
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
乔伊  我觉得现在没问题了
Well,Joey,I guess we have no problem.
就像是我的美梦终成真
It's like my favorite fairy tale come true.
公主  马童和女同性恋
The princess,the stable boy and the lesbian.
好了  你先泡配方牛奶
Okay. Okay,you start preparing the formula..
我去换盒子
and I'll start changing the box.
然后就送他们上床睡觉
And then we gotta put them straight to bed.
我们什么时候变成了那种
When did we become one of those couples..
生活围绕着老鼠转的小情侣
whose lives revolve around their rats?
因为  他们现在是我们的责任了
Well,you know what? They're our responsibility now.
好吧  这些老鼠是我们的责任
Okay,fine. These rats are our responsibility.
要是他们交配后  变成上百只呢
What happens when they mate and there are hundreds?
交配  他们是兄弟姐妹耶
Mate? They're all brothers and sisters.
是啊  但是对老鼠可不是问题
Yeah,not such a problem with rats.
他们是"爱上谁就上谁"的那种
No,they're more of a "love the one you're with" kind of animal.
才不  真的吗
No. Really?
哦  不要搞你妹妹啦
Oh,my.. Get off your sister!
我的天  我们该怎么办呢
Oh,my God. What are we gonna do?
我们有七只老鼠
The.. We have seven rats.
如果七只老鼠的每一只
So,what if each of them has seven rats..
都再生七只  那就是
and then each of those has seven rats? That's like..
我都算不过来了
That's math I can't even do!
我们该怎么办呢
What are we gonna do?
嗯  我知道这听起来很疯狂
Well,I know this is gonna sound crazy..
但我们可以不让这盒老鼠
but we could not let the box of rats
毁了我们的生活
ruin our lives.
是啊  好吧  我想你说的对
Yeah,okay. I guess you're right.
好了  我们必须送走他们
All right,so we should just give them away.
但要送给有小孩的好人家
But to nice families with children
还要有低脂全麦饼干
and reduced-fat Wheat Thins.
那些是鲍伯最喜欢的
Those were Bob's favorites.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
你一定认为我疯了
You must think I'm crazy.
不  我觉得你很善良
No,I think you're sweet.
好吧  真的好难
Good. This is just so hard.
我心里好难割舍
It's hard for me to let them go.
我猜这让我联想起很多往事
I guess it just brings back memories,you know..
就像我怀了我弟的三胞胎
from when I gave birth to my brother's triplets
最后却抛弃了他们
and I had to give them up.
我没有告诉过你那件事吗
I haven't told you about that yet,have I?
谢谢你帮我办派对  亲爱的
Thanks for the party,honey.
我应该帮你打扫吗
Should I help you clean up?
不要  你的派对结束了 现在换我的
No way. You had your party. Now I have mine.
-一切还好吧  -我只是有点累
- Is everything all right? - I just get bummed..
生日结束了
when my birthday's over.
至少有一件事值得你高兴
Well,at least you have one thing to be happy about.
你办公室那个混蛋加文没有来
That jerk,Gavin,from your office didn't show up.
是啊  他好讨厌哦
Yeah,I hate him.
我们不是在说你  我们
We weren't talking about you. We were..
好吧  来不及掩饰了  算了
No. No way to recover. No. Okay.
-一定很好玩  -嗯  是的
- Fun party. - Well,it was.
你本来会看到的  如果你不是出现在
And you would have seen it if you didn't show up at..
九点半  天啊  派对太失败了
9:30?! God! This party was lame.
再说一次  不用客气
Again,you're welcome!
听着  我把礼物给你就走人
Look,I'll just give you this and go.
你买礼物给我  为什么
You bought me a present. Why?
让我解释一下生日派对是怎样的情况
Let me explain how birthday parties usually work.
通常有礼物
There are presents..
有蛋糕  或许还有第四个或第五个人
and a cake,perhaps a fourth or fifth person.
好的  我
Okay,I..
我送礼物给你
I got you the present
弥补一下我对你的混蛋行为
to make up for being such a jerk to you.
嗯  好的  真好
Well,okay. Well,that's very nice.
而且你还写了卡片
And you wrote a card.
-"加文赠"  -肺腑之言
- "From Gavin." - I really mean it.
真美
It's beautiful.
如果你不介意  让我来
If you don't mind..? Let me.
真巧  非常合适
Well,what do you know,it fits.
瞧  加文  你是可以当个好男人的
See,Gavin. You're capable of being a nice guy.
为什么你要刁难我呢
Why do you give me such a hard time?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
莫妮卡好像认为
Well,Monica seems to think
是因为你对我有感觉
it's because you have feelings for me.
我是对你有感觉
I do have feelings for you.
真的吗
You do?
是的  我觉得你有点烦人
Yes. I feel that you're a little annoying.
为什么  加文  为什么
See,why? Gavin,why?
就在我要对你改观的时候
Right when I'm about to change my opinion of you,
你就...
you go and you..
你就这样做了
And you do that.
嘿  听着  我有东西忘了带走
Hey. Listen,I think I left something here.
是有人忘了这个  是你的吗
Well,somebody left this. Is this yours?
不是  但是我蛮喜欢的
No,but I like it.
有一只老鼠宝宝我忘了带走
No,I think I left one of my rat babies.
没  我没有看到
Well,no. I haven't seen it,
但是如果有  我会通知你的
but if I do,I'll let you know.
老鼠宝宝  老鼠宝宝
Rat baby! Rat baby!
或许就是他
Maybe that's him.